▍2026 国家银行公开赛（蒙特利尔）决赛
谢尔顿 6-3 7-6(4) 中岛布兰登 · 赛后亚军致辞
Hello everyone.
大家好
Um, first of all, big congratulations to Ben.
首先 要特别恭喜谢尔顿
Um, you know, great level this whole week.
这一整周的水准都很高
Um, congrats to you and your team,
恭喜你和你的团队
your family, uh,
还有你的家人
on incredible incredible week.
打出了了不起的一周
I think, uh,
我觉得吧
a lot of people don't realize how hard it
很多人没意识到卫冕有多难
is to go back to back, especially in uh,
尤其还是
in different cities.
两座不同的城市
So, uh, it's it's simply incredible.
所以这真的太了不起了
Uh, I'd like to say thank you to my team.
我想谢谢我的团队
Um, you know, all you guys over there.
就在那边的你们
Thank you guys so much for uh
谢谢你们的帮助
for all your help, all support.
和所有的支持
Um, not just this week,
不只是这一周
but uh but you know,
而是
my whole my whole career, so many uh
我的整个职业生涯 有那么多
so many people behind the scenes.
在幕后付出的人
So, uh really appreciate all their support
真的很感激他们的支持
for for everyone here
谢谢在场的每一位
and and also back home.
也谢谢在家乡的你们
Uh, of course, also thank you to my family.
当然 还要谢谢我的家人
My dad's over there.
我爸爸就在那边
Uh,
还有
my mom is back uh back home watching.
我妈妈在家里看着
Uh, my brother is uh in college right now.
我弟弟现在在上大学
So, uh, I really have all of them to to thank
我职业生涯的一切
for uh, for everything in my career.
都要谢谢他们
Also, big thank you to uh
还要特别感谢
to all the sponsors, all the organization uh
所有赞助商 所有组织方
in this incredible tournament.
办了这么棒的一站比赛
Um you know, I felt really great the whole
这一整周我在这儿
the whole week here.
感觉都特别好
Um and uh it really is one
这真的是
of the best best weeks of my my life.
我人生中最好的一周之一
So, uh really appreciate everyone.
所以真的很感激每一个人
all the uh all the staff, all the ball kids.
所有工作人员 所有球童
Um you guys truly do an amazing job
你们把这站比赛
with this tournament.
办得非常出色
So uh thank you guys
谢谢你们
for all your hard work.
所有的辛苦付出
Also, big thank you to all the crowd that uh
还要特别谢谢这十天里
that came out these uh these past 10 days.
来到现场的所有观众
The uh the support you guys give
你们给这站比赛
to the tournament and all the players,
和所有球员的支持
uh it's really unlike anything else.
真的是别的地方比不了的
And uh and I'm going to be honest,
我说句实话
really really enjoy here
我在蒙特利尔
in Montreal more than more than Toronto.
比在多伦多更开心
I'm not I'm not just saying
我不是因为今天
that sitting here in the final today,
坐在这里打决赛才这么说
but even before this week,
在这一周之前
really enjoy my time here.
我就很享受在这儿的时间
Thanks to uh all the people.
谢谢这里所有的人
Feels uh such like home here.
这儿感觉就像家一样
So uh really appreciate all you guys.
所以真的很感激你们
Unfortunately,
可惜
uh we'll be back in Toronto next year,
明年我们要回多伦多了
but uh but I I uh I I really look forward
但我真的很期待
to coming back here in uh in two years.
两年后再回到这里